You guys
>> I was gonna That's a good edit.
>> It's a very good question.
>> We've already had those conversations.
Maybe not. We We'll see how things go
down.
[clears throat]
>> It was a trade right?
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, what was your thinking there
when that was going down?
>> Yeah, we had targeted Colton Hood as a
guy. You know, corner is a premium
position and and a player we really
like. So, uh, you know, the fact that he
was there, um, there's some good players
taken in front of us certainly, but
really excited to get Colton where we
were able to get him and, you know,
again, add some really good depth and
competition to the the roster we
currently have.
>> Is he up in the category, Joe, of your
two previous picks of guys who love to
play football?
>> Absolutely. Absolutely. High character
kid. Um, you know, he's been at Auburn
and Colorado, then Tennessee, and, you
know, we spent some time with him at the
combine, but a kid that's tough, it
shows up on tape, like he's not afraid
to throw his body around and tackle,
he's physical, um, and and truly loves
balls.
>> How do you envision him fitting into
quarterback quarterback?
>> Uh, competing to start, you know, that's
what he's going to do. We got a good
quarterback room right now. It's amazing
how one addition changes the math in a
room and corner corn quarterback room
was good but now it's really good and
he's going to push everybody and he'll
be uh I know one thing he's planning on
coming in here and trying to win a
starting job.
>> Was there something that you guys liked
about his personality? It seemed like
when
a lot of talk down there he really
stepped up his game even more so on the
back end.
>> Yeah, he he's a phenomenal kid. again we
spent some time with him and I mean he's
just he he checks all the boxes you know
yes makeup in terms of our football and
personal character uh hard worker you
know former baseball player that has
tremendous ball skills along with traits
so checks a lot of boxes along with the
you know the football makeup that you
know that that we desire you know within
the group and add him to the other two
players that were you know that you guys
got to talk to today that were here and
um you know he fits right right in with
those guys. I know how you guys answered
this last night, but since then there
was a report that you guys had
conversations with the Saints recently
about trading for Kono. Has anything
changed on that? How likely is it Kon
stays through tonight?
>> No, nothing's changed. I wish I could
just put everything out in the Twitter
sphere and just let it let people run
with it, but no, there there's no truth
to that. We have had we've not had any
conversations today about Kavon.
>> So that's that's not true.
>> What would a scenario be then that how
would you get back into
the third round.
>> Well, we're pretty high in the fourth
round.
>> You know, we're five picks from, you
know, we had the fifth pick tomorrow, so
we're not far we're not far off from
getting
>> that would package other picks
potentially.
>> Yeah, I wasn't I wasn't thinking
anywhere near along the line what you
were thinking, but yeah, just picks that
we currently have to maybe get back into
the to the bottom of three potentially.
Joe, Joe and John, this is more a
question about yesterday's unfoldings,
but it's kind of unique to have two guys
like uh like Reese and Bailey go so
close obviously and uh there's going to
be natural comparisons here in New York
area and whatnot as football guys and
even as fans, you know,
how interesting and intriguing you think
that'll be as as their careers unfold
here, you know, even though there are
different types of players and whatnot.
I'm sure you did a lot of work on on
Bailey as well. I'm assuming
>> you're talking about CC and Bailey.
>> Yes. No. Or CC and uh
>> No, no, no. Reese. Reese and Bailey. The
two.
>> Oh, Reese and Bailey.
>> You know, obviously Jeff's taking them,
you know.
>> Yeah, that's a good question. And again,
because of our current roster and the
construction of it with the edge guys we
currently have, we put Reese under the
microscope as an inside backer. So, all
along that's that's how we were looking
at him, pairing him with Tmaine along
with the edge guys that we have and then
some of the third down stuff he could
do. So, um, you know, in that scenario,
you know, we're comparing him to Burns
and Abdul and Kavon because that that's
our current roster construction. And,
um, to add his size, speed, and
character, what we currently have and
the versatility that he has. Um, so
we're kind of looking at him in two
different roles, you know, the way Jets
are going to use Bailey and how we'll
use Ree.
>> Yeah. Do you think it'll be it'll be I
mean, you know, even though again, you
know, you're going to use them in
different ways, but two guys linebackers
picked in that, you know, in in this
town, you know, that close.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, hopefully for both cases,
they're going to be for a long time. You
know, how intriguing could that be to
see how it all unfolds?
>> Hopefully they're saying the Giants got
it right. [laughter]
I do. That's how it plays out. So,
>> you mentioned before that um the
quarterback room was good.
you know, one player who did really
good. Um, there was kind of a perception
that maybe the quarterback room was not
good for you or not good enough. Um, you
when you came in, you looked at this
room, you know, called Lot left, you
know, signed somewhere else and signed
you. So, when you looked at the room,
you kind of liked it. I mean, obviously,
we added another player.
>> Good average, not good, whatever. You
know, it's an opportunity to get better,
you know, and there's guys in there with
opportunities. I mean, I'm looking at
Trey. Trey, you know, he he hasn't
played that great. He'd tell you that.
But is he capable of playing a lot
better? I think he is. You know, that's
on that's on us and on him to get him to
play better. So, imagine if if he takes
this step. And what does that do for the
room? Is Pollson capable of playing
better than he did last year? I'd say
so, you know. So, let's go. Let's go
play better. Let's go play at a high
let's go play at a level we're capable
of playing at. You got Paulson who's a
who's a highly uh highly decorated vet
in this league. and and I after what I
saw last week, I thought he looked good.
Thought Tay looked really good last
week. So, that's kind of that's kind of
the thing I'm going I don't really care
what the perception was a year ago or
two years ago. I'm looking at what I
see. I see a good room, but I I want a
great room. I want a dominant room. I
want a bunch of I want a bunch of pit
bulls out there flying around making
plays on the football. And this Colton
Hood gives us another guy in there to do
that and compete and push everybody. So,
you put another guy in there, another
pit bull in the room. Let's see what he
does. And he plays the ball. He plays
hard. He comes from a great family.
Coached his uh his uncle in Philly. He
was a he was a corner for us, Rod Hood.
Uh so I I know the type of family this
this young man comes from, right? And
the type of person he is. I know the
kind of athlete he is. This is a this is
a this is a corner with traits and ball
skills. Traits and ball skills at
corner. Plus, he's a high character guy.
So he's gonna he's gonna light a fire in
that room. You better be ready. Better
be ready to compete.
>> You guys made a decision on Banks's
fifth year.
Uh, we're going to talk about that early
next week. Yeah.
>> Anything else,
>> Joe? Just curious. Obviously, um, we saw
Steve Tish in the room today and
yesterday. Just want to be curious, what
exactly is his position? We saw that
he's his family sold his stakes. What
exactly is his role now?
>> Yeah, he's the chairman of the team and,
you know, he's in the draft room like he
is every year.